multi_answer_questions = [
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following statements accurately describes recommended guidelines for overcoming resistance for change?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Explain the proposed changes only to the managers of the people involved.",
            "B": "Whenever possible, use technical language to describe the changes.",
            "C": "List the advantages of the proposed change.",
            "D": "Avoid relating the change to the group's existing beliefs and values.",
            "E": "If possible, introduce change gradually."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["C", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The nursing student is working to improve his time management. Which of the following would assist the nursing student in accomplishing his goal?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Identify priorities for the day.",
            "B": "Evaluate time management at the end of the day.",
            "C": "Establish a reasonable time line.",
            "D": "Plan to arrive right at start of shift.",
            "E": "Plan on his cohorts helping him."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "C"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following statements accurately describes factors that may affect an individual's growth and development?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Physical characteristics such as height, bone size, eye color, and hair color are inherited from the family of origin.",
            "B": "Fetal development can be altered by maternal age, inadequate maternal nutrition or substance abuse.",
            "C": "Abuse of alcohol and drugs is more prevalent in teenagers who have poor family relationships, low self-esteem, and poor social skills.",
            "D": "Infants who are malnourished in utero develop fewer brain cells than infants who have had adequate prenatal nutrition.",
            "E": "Environmental factors such as poverty and violence do not have a direct effect on growth and development."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The nurse is providing education on childhood safety to a group of parents. In response to a question, the nurse relates that the major causes of death in toddlers include which of the following?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Infections",
            "B": "Childhood diseases",
            "C": "Drowning",
            "D": "Motor vehicle crashes",
            "E": "Accidents"
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["C", "D", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "A nurse who provides care in a long-term care facility recognizes the need to promote health rather than solely treating illness. Which of the following measures should the nurse encourage among the older adult resident population of the facility?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Encourage frequent naps in order to ensure adequate sleep and rest.",
            "B": "Encourage residents to consume diet and energy supplements.",
            "C": "Conduct activities at a slower pace and allow residents time to respond.",
            "D": "Encourage residents to engage in the present rather than perform reminiscence.",
            "E": "Promote self-care and only assist residents when it is necessary."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["C", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following statements accurately describes how risk factors may increase a person's chances for illness or injury?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Risk factors are unrelated to the person or event.",
            "B": "All risk factors are modifiable.",
            "C": "An increase in risk factors increases the possibility of illness.",
            "D": "The presence of multiple risk factors can compound a person's risk for illness or injury.",
            "E": "Middle-aged adults are at high risk for communicable diseases."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["C", "D"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The nurse is performing an assessment on a client with a history of a dysfunctional family. What findings should the nurse anticipate?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Unhealthy personal boundaries",
            "B": "Supportive parents",
            "C": "Abuse and neglect",
            "D": "Direction and attention",
            "E": "Structured limit setting"
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "C"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is a correctly written goal?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "The client will identify five low-sodium foods by October 9.",
            "B": "The client will know the signs and symptoms of an infection.",
            "C": "The client will rate pain as a 3 or lesson a 10-point scale by 5pm today.",
            "D": "The client will understand the side effects of digoxin (Lanoxin).",
            "E": "The client will eat at least 75% of all meals by may 5."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "C", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "A registered nurse who provides care in a subacute setting is responsible for overseeing and delegating to unlicensed assistive personnel (UAP). Which of the following principles should the nurse follow when delegating to the UAP?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Ensure that UAPs closely follow the nursing process when providing care.",
            "B": "Audit the client documentation that UAPs record after they perform interventions.",
            "C": "Take frequent mini-reports from UAPs to ensure changes in client status are identified.",
            "D": "Know what clinical cues the UAP should be alert for and why.",
            "E": "Make frequent walking rounds to assess clients."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["C", "D", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which activity does the nurse engage in during evaluation?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Collect data to determine whether desired outcomes are met.",
            "B": "Assess the effectiveness of planned strategies.",
            "C": "Adjust the time frame to achieve the desired outcomes.",
            "D": "Involve the client's family in formulating desired outcomes.",
            "E": "Initiate activities to achieve the desired outcomes."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "C"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The nurse is educating a Young Childcare class and one of the parents asks what kinds of actions on his part may increase safety for his 14-month-old daughter during the next 2 years. Which of the following responses would be appropriate?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Keep medications locked away.",
            "B": "Keep plastic bags out of reach.",
            "C": "Use approved age car seats.",
            "D": "Teach to chew small food well.",
            "E": "Do not swing by arms or legs."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "C", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following clients is at an increased risk for oral problems?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Comatose client",
            "B": "Confused client",
            "C": "Depressed client",
            "D": "Uninsured client",
            "E": "Hypertensive client"
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "What would the nurse recommend to the family of a client who is diabetic, regarding foot care?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Cut the toenails very short.",
            "B": "Cut the left and right nail corners.",
            "C": "Avoid cutting into calluses.",
            "D": "Cut the nails straight across.",
            "E": "Use plenty of lotion on the feet and toes."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["C", "D"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following clients would be considered at risk for skin alterations?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "A teenager with multiple body piercings.",
            "B": "A homosexual in a monogamous relationship.",
            "C": "A client receiving radiation therapy.",
            "D": "A client undergoing cardiac monitoring.",
            "E": "A client with diabetes."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "C", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "A nurse is applying cold therapy to a client with a contusion of the arm. Which of the following is an effect of therapy?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Reduces muscle spasms.",
            "B": "Increases blood flow to tissues.",
            "C": "Constricts peripheral blood vessels.",
            "D": "Reduces the formation of edema and inflammation.",
            "E": "Increases the local release of pain-producing substances."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "C", "D"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following are functions of the skin?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Sensation",
            "B": "Protection",
            "C": "Temperature regulation",
            "D": "Immunological",
            "E": "Vitamin C production"
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "A client has sought care because of insomnia that has been increasing in severity and frequency in recent months. What questions should the nurse include in an assessment of this client's health problem?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "\"Do you smoke?\"",
            "B": "\"Do you have a family history of sleep disturbances?\"",
            "C": "\"What medications are you currently taking?\"",
            "D": "\"How would you characterize your mood lately?\"",
            "E": "\"Do you have a consistent routine around getting ready for bed and going to bed?\""
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "C", "D", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The client is newly diagnosed as having a terminal disease and asks, \"I'm going to die soon, aren't I?\" What would be appropriate replies of the nurse?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "\"Tell me how you feel.\"",
            "B": "\"No, you are not actively dying.\"",
            "C": "\"This is something I am not comfortable discussing.\"",
            "D": "\"What have you been told by your health care provider?\"",
            "E": "\"You should ask your health care provider that question.\""
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "D"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The clinic nurse sees the client today and asks about his chief complaint. The client describes to the nurse his inability to be intimate with his wife. Which of the following would be a priority for the nurse to assess?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Sleep quality",
            "B": "Medication prescribed",
            "C": "Level of stress at work",
            "D": "Social activity",
            "E": "Specifics about sexual problem"
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "C", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The nurse is caring for a female client today. As the nurse is giving the client her morning medications, she begins a conversation about her belief in a higher power. The nurse knows that this can be interpreted as which of the following?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "God",
            "B": "Faith",
            "C": "Religion",
            "D": "Atheism",
            "E": "Spirituality"
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "C", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Nurses provide many interventions to prevent falls in health care settings. Which of the following would be an appropriate intervention to prevent falls?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Keep bed in the high position.",
            "B": "Keep all side rails up at all times.",
            "C": "Apply restraints to all confused clients.",
            "D": "Lock wheels on beds and wheelchairs.",
            "E": "Clear pathway from patient's bed to bathroom."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["D", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The Joint Commission supports the client's right to pain management, and published standards for assessment and management of pain in hospitals, ambulatory care settings, and home care settings (Joint Commission 2008b). Which of the following are recommended guidelines for pain management?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Teach all clients to use a pain rating scale.",
            "B": "Determine a pain-rating goal with each client.",
            "C": "Use pharmacologic pain relief measures first.",
            "D": "Manipulate factors that affect the pain experience.",
            "E": "Keep the primary care provider in charge of all pain relief measures."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "D"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following are conditions that must be met for a person to receive the necessary data to experience the world?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "A stimulus must be present.",
            "B": "A receptor or sense organ must receive the stimulus and convert it to a nerve impulse.",
            "C": "The nerve impulse must be conducted along a nervous pathway from the receptor or sense organ to the brain.",
            "D": "The stimulus must be recognized by the cardiovascular system and sent to the brain.",
            "E": "The person must physically and mentally recognize the stimulus and accept or reject it in the brain.",
            "F": "A particular area in the brain must receive and translate the impulse into a sensation."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "C", "F"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The nurse is caring for client 82 years of age who is struggling to adapt to hearing loss as he ages. The nurse performs which of the following interventions to assist the client in adapting to this sensory deficit?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Make sure he wears his hearing aid.",
            "B": "Speak in a lower tone of voice.",
            "C": "Speak so he can observe your lip motions.",
            "D": "Keep his environment clear of clutter.",
            "E": "Orient to person, place, and time frequently."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "C"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following are examples of incidental disclosures of client health information that are permitted?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "A nurse working in a physician's office puts out a sign-in sheet for incoming clients",
            "B": "Two nurses are overheard talking about a client through the door of an empty client room.",
            "C": "A nurse places a client chart in a holder on the examining room door with the name facing out.",
            "D": "A nurse leaves an x-ray on a light board in the hallway that leads to the examining rooms",
            "E": "A nurse calls out the name of a client who is seated in the waiting room."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following are examples of breaches of client confidentiality?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "A nurse discusses a client with a coworker in the elevator.",
            "B": "A nurse shares her computer password with a relative of a client.",
            "C": "A nurse checks the medical record of a client to see who should be called in an emergency.",
            "D": "A nurse updates the employer of a client regarding the client's return to work.",
            "E": "A nurse uses a computer to document a client's response to pain medication."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "D"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "In which of the following cases should a progress note be written?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "For any nurse-client interaction.",
            "B": "When admitting a client.",
            "C": "When receiving a client postoperatively.",
            "D": "When assisting a client with ADLs.",
            "E": "When a procedure is performed."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["B", "C", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "A nurse researching a diet for a client with diabetes includes foods that supply energy to the body. Which of the following are classes of nutrients that supply this energy?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Vitamins",
            "B": "Proteins",
            "C": "Fats",
            "D": "Minerals",
            "E": "Carbohydrates"
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["B", "C", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following factors increase BMR?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Growth",
            "B": "Infection",
            "C": "Fever",
            "D": "Emotional tension",
            "E": "Aging"
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "A client visits the health care facility for a scheduled physical assessment. What should the nurse do when physically assessing the quality of the client's oxygenation?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Monitor the client's respiratory rate.",
            "B": "Note the amount of oxygen administered.",
            "C": "Check the symmetry of the client's chest.",
            "D": "Observe the breathing pattern and effort.",
            "E": "Check the devices used to deliver oxygen."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "C", "D"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The nurse is caring for a girl 13 years of age, who is admitted after taking some of her mother's sleeping pills. She is withdrawn and declines to eat or engage in conversation, except to say she doesn't like herself. The nurse is aware that potential causes of poor self-concept at this age can be related to which of the following?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Inability to accept bodily changes.",
            "B": "Identity confusion.",
            "C": "Failure to accept role responsibility.",
            "D": "Failure to develop meaningful goals.",
            "E": "Inability to resolve child versus adult roles."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The nurse cares for a successful chemical engineer, age 29 years, who is admitted with a respiratory infection. The client reports feeling more stress than ever since a job promotion six months ago and asks, \"Why would something so positive and wonderful cause so much stress for me?\" Which is an appropriate response by the nurse?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "All major life events can cause stress for us.",
            "B": "People vary greatly in their perception of what constitutes as a crisis or stressor.",
            "C": "Your job promotion probably has nothing to do with the stress you feel.",
            "D": "Positive life events do not cause stress or illness.",
            "E": "Even positive life events can affect us in negative ways."
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "B", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The nurse is caring for a female client 64 years of age who is admitted for knee replacement. As the nurse performs the shift assessment, the client comments, \"I wouldn't mind getting old if I were not for the physical losses, like the wrinkles, all the drooping, and the wearing out of everything. People like to be around youthful, beautiful men and women; I feel so unattractive.\" Is the client correct about how society view older people? In general, which of the following does society emphasize and reward?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Wisdom and sharing",
            "B": "Youthfulness",
            "C": "Mentoring the inexperienced",
            "D": "Health and fitness",
            "E": "Physical attractiveness"
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["B", "D", "E"]
    },
    {
        "Question": "The nurse is assessing his client's self-concept. The client is status post-myocardial infarction and is due to be discharged tomorrow. Which of the following focuses will give the nurse the most information about the client's self-concept?",
        "Options": {
            "A": "Body image",
            "B": "Gender identity",
            "C": "Self-esteem",
            "D": "Role performance",
            "E": "Sexual orientation"
        },
        "CorrectAnswers": ["A", "C", "D"]
    }]
